popularproductsonline.com 2012-10-23

# 

## What We Do With Your Personal Information

Active Date: October 26, 2010  
Previous Revisions: None. 

### Our Privacy Policy 

This privacy policy is intended to inform you about our collection, use, and protection of your personal and other information in regards to our “Promotion” and our web site, the “Promotion Site” as well as inform certain Californian residents about their California Rights. For more information about this Promotion, the Promotion Site and the Promotional Path of third party advertiser Offers, please read the Terms and Conditions. Capitalized terms such as Promotion and Promotional Path in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as set out in the Terms and Conditions. 

Please read this Policy carefully to understand what we (also referred to as the “Company”) do with the personal and other information that we collect from you both online and offline. 

PLEASE NOTE: WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO REVISE THIS PRIVACY POLICY AT ANY TIME SIMPLY BY POSTING A REVISION, SO WE ENCOURAGE YOU TO REVIEW IT PERIODICALLY FOR CHANGES. IN ORDER TO TRACK CHANGES, WE WILL INCLUDE A HISTORICAL REFERENCE AT THE TOP OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. 

### Acknowledgement/Agreement

This web site is not intended for use by individuals under the age of eighteen or those who are not legal residents of the United States. By using the web site and/or by submitting information to us, you consent to our collection and use of this information in accordance with the provisions of this Privacy Policy. If you are not 18 years of age or you are not a United States resident or do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, then do not use this web site and do not participate in the Promotion. 

WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO REVISE THIS POLICY AT ANY TIME SIMPLY BY POSTING A REVISION, SO WE ENCOURAGE YOU TO REVIEW IT PERIODICALLY FOR CHANGES. IN ORDER TO TRACK CHANGES, WE WILL INCLUDE A HISTORICAL REFERENCE AT THE TOP OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. 

  1. **How we collect information (personal and otherwise) from you:**
    1. **Voluntary Information Submitted.** Voluntarily and visibly by your completion of online registration, information forms or surveys or by you contacting our customer service department. The personally identifiable information we collect in this way likely includes: your name, mailing and email address, phone number, age, date of birth, gender, your product and service preferences. If you do not wish to provide us with this personally identifiable information, PLEASE DO NOT REGISTER AND PLEASE DO NOT PARTICIPATE IN THE PROMOTION NOR TAKE ADVANTAGE OF ANY OF THE ADVERTISER OFFERS. 
    2. **Involuntary Information Collected from You.** Involuntarily and invisibly via a third party or by way of various technologies we use and advertisers may use when you connect to and/or use our web site and the Promotional Path. We currently use cookies and beacons (also known as pixel tags and identifiers) as background technologies because they permit us to present a better Promotion, make navigation of the Promotional Path easier by the user and permit us to track completion of advertiser Offers on the Promotional path. The types of information which we collect technologically or via a third-parties is not generally personally identifiable information and includes standard computer user as well as other generic information logged by our servers (such as Your computer's IP address, time of viewing, type of browser used to view, the computer operating system, etc.) and ‘click through’ data (the record of your click through selections from advertiser Offers within the Promotional Path). 
    3. **Use of Existing Technology.** Cookies are tiny files containing small bits of information that a web browser stores on the hard drive of a personal computer at our request. Cookies enable us to remember users and user information from one session to another, thereby enabling us to provide better individualized service and pre-filled forms for your convenience. Pixel tags are small strings of code that are placed on a web site to monitor the behavior of users visiting the web site (and in this case the Promotional path) and to track which advertising offers a user views and chooses to complete. 
    4. **Disabling Cookies.** If you do not wish to provide us with this non personally identifiable information, then you can either a) disable cookies in your web browser options (Go to your browsers “Help” to learn how to do this) or obtain appropriate software to enable you to surf the web anonymously. However, disabling cookies will affect the ease with which and possibly your ability to participate in the Promotion or alternately b), simply choose not to register and participate in the Promotion and navigate your browser away from our web site and the Promotional Path. 
    5. **Reserving Right to Use New Technologies.** The use of web technologies is rapidly evolving and we reserve the right to use new technologies as they are developed and strongly urge you to revisit this privacy policy for any updates regarding its use of newer technologies. 
    6. **Anonymized Data.** We also collect anonymized data to calculate aggregate statistical information, to identify the number of users and participants in the Promotion, the number of users who clicked through specific advertising Offers on the Promotional Path, the numbers of users who completed such Offers, and to measure traffic patterns to our web site and through the Promotion path. This data does not identify individual users, but may be used for general statistical, marketing and auditing purposes. 
    7. **Preference Data –“Target or Behavioral Advertising”** If the Promotion path includes what is known as a “Coregistration or Coreg Path”, we will also collect data regarding your geographic location and Internet behavior (i.e. browsing, search, shopping, purchase and ad response behavior) known as “Preference Data” via the use of cookies and pixel tags explained above and communications with Advertisors on the Promotional Path. This Preference Data is generally used to present you with more useful and relevant advertising and advertiser Offers – for example by showing Los Angeles newspaper ads to someone from Los Angeles or by displaying book ads to someone who frequents online bookstores or someone who has just completed a book related offer in the Promotional path. 
  2. **Ways that we use the information, both Personally Identifiable and Non-Personally Identifiable.**

WE MAY USE AN INDIVIDUAL'S PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION FOR 

_ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE IN THE COMPANY’S SOLE DISCRETION_ INCLUDING PROVIDING TO THIRD PARTIES FOR SECONDARY MARKETING PURPOSES. 

Currently, we use information for at least the following purposes: 

    1. **Administration of the Promotion** (sharing your personal info and other information with other advertisers involved in the Promotion – they may also share information about you with us), the fulfillment of the Promotion – contacting you or sending you the gift, confirming advertising Offers have been completed and verifying with third parties that you are a genuine bona fide consumer. 
    2. **Pre-selecting and pre-filling your contact and other information** for advertiser Offers which form part of the Promotional Path. 
    3. **Use in our own and our affiliated companies online and offline marketing programs** which may include email marketing, telephone marketing and SMS messaging to any cell phone number provided to us. 
    4. **Notifying the IRS** that a participant has received a gift (if the amount is over the threshold where we are required to notify the IRS). 
    5. **Sharing, licensing, or selling your personally identifiable information to any third parties for secondary online and/or offline marketing purposes in our sole discretion.**
    6. **To facilitate a business transfer** (if for example, our business was sold). 
    7. **To maintain and share with third parties suppression lists or opt out lists.**
    8. **Targeted or Behavioral Advertising.** We use information collected from you voluntarily and involuntary through your completion of registration, any surveys, your use of the Promotional Path, your use of search engines, etc. to show you advertising and products which we believe will be of interest to you. 

IF YOU DO NOT WISH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION USED IN THIS WAY, PLEASE DO NOT REGISTER ON OUR WEB SITE AND PLEASE DO NOT PARTICIPATE IN THE PROMOTION. 

  3. **Dissemination of Individual Information.**
    1. **Sale or Transfer to third parties.**  
COMPANY MAY SELL OR TRANSFER INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE IN COMPANY’S SOLE DISCRETION. 
    2. **Promotion Fulfillment and Verification.**  
Company will transfer individual information to third parties when necessary to provide a product or service that a person orders from such third party while using the Promotional Path or when responding to Sponsor Offers.

We will also use third party verification services to verify your address and phone number and that you are in fact a legitimate consumer. 

    3. **Legal Process.**  
Share with third parties when (1) trying to protect or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; (2) investigating fraud that has already taken place; (3) enforcing or applying existing terms and conditions and/or other agreements; (4) protecting the rights, property or safety of our web site, our users and business associates including advertisers; (5) responding to subpoenas, court orders or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 
    4. **Summary Data.**  
Company may sell or transfer non-individualized information, such as summary or aggregated anonymous information about all persons or sub-groups of persons. 
    5. **Access.**  
Individuals have access to their individual information collected to provide an opportunity for an individual to correct, amend, or delete such information. Access can be obtained by contacting [privacy@popularproductsonline.com](mailto:privacy@popularproductsonline.com). Company may also grant advertising clients and email services providers’ access to an individual’s email address to verify the origin of the Individual Information collected. 
  4. **Third parties use of your Information – Privacy Practices of third parties**

Company has no control over the advertisers who form part of the Promotional path or how they use the personally identifiable information we provide to them when you elect to complete one of their Offers. Their privacy policies and the terms of use for their web sites are distinct from Companies and we urge you to read their privacy policies and terms of use before participating in any of their Offers. Company has no control over privacy policies of third parties with whom we provide information for secondary marketing purposes. 

  5. **Security of your information stored by us**

We use commercially reasonable efforts to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, or accidental loss or destruction of your information (including the use of firewalls) but given the nature of the Internet and the internet advertising and promotional industry where information about you passes through entities not controlled by us we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent your information from being illegally accessed, stolen or altered. In addition, your information is shared with third parties whose privacy, business and security policies and practices are not within our control. 

  6. **Communicating with Children**

This web site and the Promotional Path are for persons 18 years of age and older ONLY. We are committed to protecting the privacy of children and it is our intention to be fully compliant with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“Coppa”). To follow Coppa guidelines, we do not knowing collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that a child under the age of thirteen has provided us with such information through any point of contact, please contact our Privacy Officer and we will ensure such information is deleted from our records. In addition, your information is shared with third parties whose privacy, business and security policies and practices are not within our control. 

  7. **What choices do I have regarding the use of my personal information?**
    1. You can opt out of receiving any further information from us about the Promotion and our products and services and stop us from sharing your personal information with third parties including the advertiser by contacting: 

Ace Brands Online Inc. – Privacy Officer  
24-155 East Beaver Creek Road  
Suite 233, Richmond Hill, L4B 3J9  

    2. If you want to stop third parties (such as other advertisers in the Promotional path) with whom we have already provided information from using that information, you need to reference their privacy policy and contact them directly about this issue. 
  8. **Correcting, deleting or accessing your personal information**

If you believe that the personal information that we hold about you is incorrect, or if you wish us to remove any information held about you, you may contact our Privacy Officer to ask us to update or delete that personal information. To update or delete your information please contact the Privacy Officer by writing to: 

Ace Brands Online Inc. – Privacy Officer  
24-155 East Beaver Creek Road  
Suite 233, Richmond Hill, L4B 3J9  

  9. **Individuals Outside of the United States**

Anyone using our web site outside of the United States acknowledges that personal information will be collected and stored by the Company in the United States. By registering on this Website and using the Promotion, you consent to the transfer of information to and/or storage of information outside of your country and in the United States. 

  10. **California and other state special privacy rights**
    1. If you are a resident of the state of California or another state with laws relating to the privacy of your personal information, you may have specific and additional rights that are not set out in this privacy policy. 
    2. Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal customer information we have shared with third parties or corporate affiliates for those third parties or corporate affiliates' direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which the information was shared, along with their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: 

Ace Brands Online Inc. – Privacy Officer  
24-155 East Beaver Creek Road  
Suite 233, Richmond Hill, L4B 3J9  

    3. In your request, please specify that you want a "Your Ace Brands Online Inc. California Privacy Rights Notice ". Please allow 30 days for a response. 

Copyright © Popularproductsonline. All rights reserved.
